fishbowlinventory.com 2007-12-10

# Fishbowl Inventory - Privacy Statement

**1\. Site covered by this Privacy Statement**

This Privacy Statement applies to the http://www.fishbowlinventory.com domain.

**Links to non-Fishbowl Inventory websites**

The Fishbowl Inventory website may provide links to third-party websites for your convenience and information. If you access those links, you will leave the Fishbowl Inventory website. Fishbowl Inventory does not control those sites or their privacy practices, which may differ from Fishbowl Inventory's. We do not endorse or make any representations about third-party websites. The personal data you choose to give to unrelated third parties is not covered by the Fishbowl Inventory Privacy Statement. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any company before submitting your personal information. Some third-party companies may choose to share their personal data with Fishbowl Inventory; that sharing is governed by that third-party company's privacy policy.

**2\. Types of information we collect**

This Privacy Statement covers personal information, non-personal data collection and aggregate reporting.

  * **Personal information**

is information that is associated with your name or personal identity. Fishbowl Inventory uses personal information to understand better your needs and interests and to provide you with better service. Once you choose to provide us with personal information, you can be assured it will be used only to support your customer relationship with Fishbowl Inventory. We take seriously the trust you place in us. Fishbowl Inventory will not sell, rent or lease your personal information to others.

  * **Non-personal information**

is data about usage and service operation that is not associated with a specific personal identity. Fishbowl Inventory collects and analyzes non-personal information to evaluate how visitors use the Fishbowl Inventory website. Non-personal data we collect may include the pages visited on the Fishbowl Inventory website, unique URLs(1) visited within www.fishbowlinventory.com, browser type and IP(2) address. Most non-personal data is collected via analysis technologies. Fishbowl Inventory Web pages use technologies for data analysis and personalization services.

**3\. Children's privacy**

Fishbowl Inventory is committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities and interests. Fishbowl Inventory does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 and Fishbowl Inventory does not target its websites to children under 13.

**4\. How we use your information**

Fishbowl Inventory uses your personal information to provide you with requested services and to help us better understand your needs and interests. Specifically, we use your information to help you complete a transaction or order, to communicate with you, to provide service and support, to update you on services and benefits and to personalize promotional offers.

Personal data collected online may also be combined with information you provide Fishbowl Inventory through other sources such as product registration, call centers or public events such as trade shows or seminars.

Personal data given to Fishbowl Inventory may be transferred across state and country borders for the purposes of data consolidation, storage and simplified customer information management.

Non-personal data is aggregated for reporting about Fishbowl Inventory website usability, performance and effectiveness. It is used to improve the customer experience, usability and site content.

**5\. Who we share your information with**

Fishbowl Inventory will not sell, rent or lease your personal information to others. Fishbowl Inventory will not share your personal information with third parties except in responding to your requests for products or services. Your permission will be requested when you submit your information. Fishbowl Inventory shares customer information across Fishbowl Inventory-owned business entities and companies working on our behalf, but only as described above in "How we use your information."

Fishbowl Inventory contracts with third-party service providers and suppliers to deliver complete products, services and customer solutions described in "How we use your information." Suppliers and service providers are required to keep confidential the information received on behalf of Fishbowl Inventory and may not use it for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for Fishbowl Inventory. These service providers may change or we may contract with additional service providers to better accommodate our customers. Fishbowl Inventory will not share personal information with any other third parties without your permission, unless required by law enforcement action, subpoena, or local law.

Fishbowl Inventory or its related entities could merge with or be acquired by another business entity or some or all of their respective assets could be acquired. If such a combination or acquisition occurs, Fishbowl Inventory will make every reasonable effort to notify you in the event we share with the merging or acquiring entity some or all of your personal information to continue serving you.

**6\. Your choices**

Fishbowl Inventory gives you the choice of receiving a variety of information that complements our products and services. You can subscribe to receive certain product- and service-specific information and marketing communications. These communications may include new product information, special offers, or an invitation to participate in market research.

**7\. Keeping your information secure**

Fishbowl Inventory is committed to protecting the information you provide us. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, to maintain data accuracy, and to ensure the appropriate use of the information, Fishbowl Inventory has in place appropriate physical and managerial procedures to safeguard the information we collect.

**8\. Changes to this Statement**

If there are updates to the terms of Fishbowl Inventory's Online Privacy Statement, we will post those changes and update the revision date in this document, so you will always know what information we collect online, how we use it, and what choices you have.

**9\. Contacting us**

We value your opinions. If you have comments or questions about our privacy policy, please write to us at the following address:

Fishbowl Inventory   
580 E. Technology Ave.   
Suite C2500   
Orem, UT 84097 

_Rev. October 2005_

1A URL (Uniform Resource Locator) is the global address of documents and other resources on the World Wide Web. For example, [http://www.fishbowlinventory.com](http://www.fishbowlinventory.com/) is the URL for Fishbowl Inventory's home page.

2An IP address is an identifier for a computer or device on a Transmission Control Protocol/Internet Protocol (TCP/IP) network, such as the World Wide Web. Networks use the TCP/IP protocol to route information based on the IP address of the destination. In other words, an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web, allowing Web servers to locate and identify your computer. Computers require IP addresses in order for users to communicate on the Internet, browse and shop.

| 

Give us a ring  
1.800.774.7085

With Fishbowl Inventory we got a quality piece of software, but more importantly, a team of "can do" people who are incredibly competent, positive, and client focused. I really feel that they are invested in helping us to be as successful as possible using the tool that they have developed.  
 _BooJee Beads_  
 _President_

Fishbowl Inventory is very easy to use. The tool was wisely developed to mirror all of the logical steps in business. My employees have been able to adopt Fishbowl Inventory in their daily routine without a large amount of training.  
 _Backyard Adventures_  
 _Chris Connors_  
  
---|---
